kswiss.com 2019-10-25

# Privacy Policy - K-Swiss

* K-Swiss uses cookies only to allow you to use the kswiss.com website in the most efficient manner. Cookies allow us to enhance and personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. By way of example, our use of cookies enable us to “remember” the items in your shopping cart, recognize you when you return to the site, and collect other non-personal identifiable information to analyze visitor behavior such as IP address, browser type and other unique device identifiers.

If you wish, you may have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you may choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Please note, however, that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our website.

We also work with other companies who use tracking technologies, including web beacons, to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our website and about your interaction with our communications, including advertising and e-mails. If you object to web beacons, you may follow the instructions for deleting existing cookies and disabling future cookies. We will still know how many of our e-mails are opened and we will automatically receive your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access devices, but we will not identify you as an individual.

* Except as described in this Privacy Policy, K-Swiss does not sell, rent or trade any personal information you provide to us online or at our stores, nor do we share such information with third parties. We may disclose personal information about you to third parties who provide services to us and who agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfilment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, website evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. We may need to share personal information with these third parties so that they can perform these services; however, we limit the personal information that we give to them and authorize them to use this information only for the purpose of performing those services.

In proceeding with your online order, you agree that both your name and address and those of the delivery name and address (if different) will be checked using third parties such as credit agencies. If you are providing a delivery name and address that is not your own, you must have that person’s permission to give us their personal information and for us to use it for the purposes specified. By providing their name and address, you are telling us that you have their permission.

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with certain business agents and vendors, so that they can provide marketing analysis and advise us on advertising strategies. This information does not identify individual users. From time to time, we also may share non-personal information (such as the number of users who visited the website during a specific time period or who purchased a specific product through the website) with our marketing partners, advertisers and others. This information is usually shared in an aggregated form.

We may release personal information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; if we have been advised by counsel; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of K-Swiss or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or others.

As with any business, it is possible that as our business develops, we might go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, sale of all or a portion of our assets or the purchase of online stores or other assets. In such cases, information about customers will likely be transferred. If that happens, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the privacy policy in effect.

Personal information submitted to or collected through this website may be stored and/or processed in the United States for the purposes described in this privacy policy. By using K-Swiss products and services (including our website), you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

If you would like to opt-out of receiving ads tailored by 3rd party tracking technologies associated with our website, please click here. If you opt-out from these third party tracking technologies, you may still see our ads at other websites, but the ads will not be tailored using third party tracking technologies associated with our website.
